igloo.com 2016-10-11

# Buy & Sell Domains on Igloo.com

Effective Date: 08/03/2015

Igloo.com, Ltd. ("us," "we," or "Igloo.com") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its users of or visitors to the domain, sub-domains, and affiliated domains of www.Igloo.com.com (collectively, the "Site") and/or utilizing Igloo.com's domain marketplace services (the "Services"). We created this Igloo.com Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. 

The TRUSTe certification applies to the following properties: www.igloo.com 

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

**Section 1. Information Collection Practices.**

Section 1.1. Types of Information Collected.

a. Personal Information Collected. In order for you to access aspects of the Site or Service, we require you to obtain a user account and provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address) and (2) Financial Data (such as your bank account, tax ID and/or credit card number). If you communicate with us by e-mail, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. 

Section 1.2. Uses of Information Collected.

a. Company Use of the Information. We use Contact Data to contact you when necessary, facilitate contact and negotiations between you and other Igloo.com users or to send you information about our company or our services. We use your Financial Data to verify your qualifications to participate in certain aspects of services and to facilitate domain purchases and sales. 

b. Sharing of Personal Information. We share certain categories of information we collect from you only in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We share your Contact Data and Financial Data with Igloo.com's parent company, Igloo.com Limited which shall uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Igloo.com, send you information about their company and their services, and when necessary to have your user accounts with the various companies interact. We maintain a procedure for you to review and request changes to your Personal Information; this procedure is described in Section 2.1, below. 

c. Exceptional disclosure of information. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; (b) protect our rights or property, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; (c) if Igloo.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, in which case you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, or (d) enforce the Igloo.com User Agreement. 

d. Service Providers. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

e. User Choice Regarding Collection, Use, and Distribution of Personal Information. You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those aspects of the Site and/or Services that require your Personal Information. 

Section 1.3. Tracking Technologies / Cookies

a. We and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. 

b. Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

c. As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

d. Web Beacons. We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

e. 3rd Party Tracking. The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies to provide us with web analytics data, which we use to continually improve the Site. 

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personally identifiable information. 

f. Behavioral Targeting. Re-Targeting. We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

g. We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. 

**Section 2. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information.**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@igloo.com](mailto:support@igloo.com). 

Section 2.1. User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information.

a. Information Access. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or ask to have it removed by making the change in your user account setting page, by emailing our Customer Support at [support@igloo.com](mailto:support@igloo.com) or by contacting us by telephone contact information listed below. We will responde to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

b. Data Retention. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

c. Opt-Out Preferences. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [support@igloo.com](mailto:support@igloo.com). 

Section 2.2. Lost or Stolen Information.

You must promptly notify us if your username or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that username or password from your account and update our records accordingly. 

Section 2.3. Third Party Links and Technologies.

a. Links to 3rd party sites. Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Igloo.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

b. Facebook Connect. You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

c. Widgets and Applets. Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, the Share this button and interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Section 3. Updates and Changes to the Policy.**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

**Section 4. Contact information**

Igloo.com  
Level 4, 55 Anzac Avenue  
Auckland 1010, New Zealand 

Phone (US/Canada FREE): 1 800 477 8207  
Phone (Worldwide): +1 508 689 9569
